Diana Davies Papers, 1960s-1996 (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Artwork and Design by Diana Jo Davies
  - Miscellaneous themes and portraits - designs and drawings (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Videotapes by Diana Jo Davies (Box 41)
- Additional Material
  - Oral history of Diana Davies, interviewed by Aimee Brown and Laura Finkel: CD and transcript, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Oversize prints - various themes (some are duplicates of smaller prints in the regular files)
  - Women's Movement and Women's Lives
    - Women in public market, Portugal circa 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Three lifelong friends (3 older women in Parish hall) (Box 43)
    - "Woman" African-Amer. woman holding sigh, surrounded by 2 profiles (Box 43)
    - Shirley Chisholm, Andrea Dworkin, Bella Abzug, Kate Millett (Box 43)
    - Tower press. women's printshop, NY 1970s (Box 43)
    - Men picket the 1970 Women's Strike march, NY (Box 43)
    - 2 collages of women's faces (photos) (Box 43)
  - Labor History: Dolores Huerta Chicanas from UFW, Cesar Chavez (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Native American Rights: Three older women with "Indian Power Sigh" (1968) Miscellaneous portraits, demos (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Dance
    - Choreographer and dancer - "Imogene" NY City, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Man dancing in fountain, NY City 1966. Lincoln Center (Box 43)
    - Dancer in a Bowery Bar, 1960s (Box 43)
  - Artists and Craftspeople - photographers, filmmakers, actors (film)
    - Francine Winham-1967 - filmmaker/photographer. London (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Alexander Calder, sculptor. 1960s NY City; Gina Lollabrigida, actor (film) 1960s (Box 43)
  - Peace movement
    - Various demonstrations, 1960s (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Women protesters in "the tombs" jail, NYC 1967 (Box 43)
    - Stop the Draft Week (Box 43)
  - Poverty/Poor folk
    - Portraits, demos, street scenes, homeless people (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Buffalo Creek Hollow Damn disaster, 1972; W. Virginia - survivors, ruin (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Writers
    - Jimmy Breslin (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Norman Mailer (Box 43)
    - Jean Genet (Box 43)
  - Street scenes - hither and yon
    - Portraits, street scenes, miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Old woman leaning against storefront, NY City (anon.), 1960s (Box 43)
  - Children: Miscellaneous portraits (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights Movement/ African-American History
    - Afeni Shakur, 1968 (Black painter) (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Coretta Scott King, 1968 (Box 43)
  - Musicians
    - Janis Joplin, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Leontyne Price, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Ethel Merman (Box 43)
    - John Lennon, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Politics/Politicians: Eugene McCarthy, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Theatre
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - "Death of Gargoyles" performer, 1971 (Box 43)
  - The Right Wing: Pro-war in Vietnam demos, Anti-Communits, U.S. Nazis, 1960s (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Animals/creatures: Cat, "Max," in window (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Photojourney (from the book)
    - Bessie who lives in Central park, NY City, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - 2 women, poor people's march- on the road, 1968 (Box 43)
    - The Bowery Boys, NY, 1965 (Box 43)
- "Oversize" published material and posters (from portfolios and files), work done for:
  - The program in Black American Culture and Smithsonian Performing Arts - Smithsonian Institution (Box 44)
  - Win Magazine (Box 44)
  - World Outlook Magazine (Box 44)
  - The New York Times (Box 44)
  - Fawcett/Premier Books (Box 44)
  - Epoca Magazine (Italy) (Box 44)
  - The Christian Science Monitor (Box 44)
  - Photography Annual (Box 44)
  - The Village Voice (Box 44)
  - Panorama Magazine (Italy) (Box 44)
  - Dateline Magazine - Overseas Press Club of America (Box 44)
  - Sojourner (Box 44)
  - NY Times Magazine (Box 44)
  - The Boston Globe (Box 44)
  - The Daily News (NY) (Box 44)
  - Women's Rights National Historical Park (Box 44)
  - The Waldo Independent (Box 44)
  - New Society Publishers (Box 44)
  - Love It Like a Fool - video stills - film about Malvina Reynolds (Box 44)
  - Photojourney - photos by Diana Davies (book) (Box 44)
  - Pure Lust, Beacon Press - author photo of Mary Daly (Box 44)
  - Dirty Linen, the Journal of Folk and World Music (Box 44)
  - Univ. of Georgia Press (Box 44)
  - Heart and Soul, film and production stills (Box 44)
  - Life Magazine (Box 44)
  - Liberation Magazine (Box 44)
  - Newsweek Magazine (Box 44)
  - Die Zeit, newspaper, Germany (Box 44)
  - Tilbury House Publishers (Box 44)
  - Macmillan Co. (publishers) (Box 44)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston (Box 44)
  - Rutgers Univ. Press (Box 44)
  - Surviva, film and productions stills - for Women Make Movies (Box 44)
  - Greene County Council on the Arts News (Box 44)
  - Mammy, a third world women's publication, published by RAT Magazine (Box 44)
  - Tenant, published by the Metropolitan Council on Housing, NY City (Box 44)
  - Thomas Y. Crowell and Co. Publishers (Box 44)
  - The Power of the People (book) (Box 44)
  - Oak Publications (Box 44)
  - The NY Times Scool Weekly (Box 44)
  - World Magazine (Box 44)
  - 13th Moon - journal (Box 44)
  - Sing Out! The Folk Music Magazine (Box 44)
  - AMSCO Music Publishing Co. (Box 44)
  - Smithsonian Magazine (Box 44)
  - Ms. magazine (Box 44)
  - Heresies - journal (Box 44)
  - Alfred A. Knopf, publishers, NY (Box 44)
  - Transaction - Social Science journal (Box 44)
  - Anchor/Doubleday Publishers (Box 44)
  - Ginn Publishers (Box 44)
  - Smithsonian - folkways recordings (Box 44)
  - Syracuse Univ. Press (Box 44)
  - Fatos e Fatos (Brasil) Magazine (Box 44)
  - Artcetera (journal) (Box 44)
  - Saturday Review (Box 44)
  - The Washington Post (Box 44)
  - Dell Publishers (Box 44)
  - Art Underground…and Beyond, Artfellows Gallery, Maine (Box 45)
  - The Maine Progressive (Newspaper) (Box 45)
  - Portrait exhibition poster, Beetle's lunch (Box 45)
  - Debbie Fier Music poster (Box 45)
  - Sonia Johnson presidential campaign poster (photo for poster) (Box 45)
  - "It Cheers me to pretend I'm playing music" - Kady poster - photo (Box 45)
  - Diana Davies and Big Red Lucy - Music poster "An Almost-April Fools show" (Flywheel Arts) (Box 45)
  - Sistervision Exhibition poster, 2000 (SSC, Smith College) (Box 45)
  - Arlo Guthrie poster (Box 45)
  - Muhammad Ali poster (Box 45)
  - Frances Crowe poster (Box 45)
  - ABC/with FIST (Anarchist Black Cross - prisoners' rights group) (Box 45)
  - "War kills. Stop the war" - anti-Gulf war poster design (Box 45)
  - "Free Mumia" pencil design for silk screen t-shirts (Box 45)
  - G.E.O. - solidarity is our strength (G.E.O., UMass, Amherst, 1998) (Box 45)
  - Food Not Bombs - several poster designs (Box 45)
  - Uncommon Carnival - poster and silkscreen for t-shirt designs (R.A.Y. -Revolutionary Anarchist Youth) (Box 45)
  - Labor history living wage event poster and program design (AFSC) (Box 45)
  - Jobs and living wage campaign comic strip - "Poor Folk Funny Papers" (Box 45)
  - The Baker Dreams of the Farm - poster for Annette Rubino - Buckley, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Flywheel - logo design, 1999 (Box 45)
  - "The Work Walk" drawings by DJD - collage poster for AFSC (Box 45)
  - "Tierra y Libertad - Emiliano Zapata" design for poster and t-shirt silkscreen, 1994 (Box 45)
  - Some newspaper clippings and posters for Diana Davies music shows (Box 45)
- Found and created goods (oversize and odd objects)
  - Silkscreen
    - T-shirts I've made (Box 46)
    - Tote-bag, "Grrrls Rock" (Box 46)
  - Political buttons (Box 46)
- Negatives
  - Negs # 1 through 106 (Box 47)
  - Negs # 107 through 203 (Box 48)
  - Negs # 204 through 324 (Box 49)
  - Negs # 325 through 423 (Box 50)
  - Negs # 424 through 516 (Box 51)
  - Negs # 517 through 612 (Box 52)
  - Negs # 613 through 720 (Box 53)
  - Negs # 721 through 822 (Box 54)
  - Negs # 823 through 942 (Box 55)
  - Negs # 943 through 1065 (Box 56)
  - Negs --2 ¼ x 2 ¼ (various numbers) (Box 57)